
Installation Guide:

1. Copy folder app, skin, js to magento root folder
2. Make sure to clear cache in admin of magento
3. Go to System/Configuration, Credit is on the left side. Click on it and change the configuration as you wish.
4. Refresh the frontend and see how Credit Extension works.

Note that:

If at the first time  you login admin after installing extension, then you see message "access denied", please try to logout and login again
